[SINGING] Designing emails can be really tough.
在設計郵件可真難熬。
Client preprocessors can be pretty rough.
客戶端預處理器可以說是相當粗糙。
To code email for all their devices,
要編寫所有裝置的電子郵件程式碼，
cut the design into many slices.
將設計切隔成許多區塊。
Mark it up in tables with inline style,
將它用內嵌的方式加入在表格中，
with media queries into one big file.
和media queries放在同一個檔案中。
To win, you'll train and learn the details ??
要贏，你會學習和練習這些細節。
Unmasking HTML Emails!
揭露 HTML電子郵件！
Welcome back.
歡迎回來。
This is level five.
這是五階段。
In modern front-end development, it's very popular to use a mobile-first approach.
在現代的前端開發，以行動裝置為優先的開發是非常受歡迎的。
In this approach, you would create a layout for small screens using a minimal amount of CSS.
在這種趨勢中，您將創建一個使用最少的CSS給小螢幕使用的本文。
You would then add CSS via media queries as the screen size grew.
你將透過media queries來加入CSS適應螢幕尺寸的成長。
Without consistent media query support in email clients,
在沒有支援media query的郵件接收裝置上，
we have to take a different approach.
我們要採取不同的方法。
In this level, we're going to create a two-column layout
在這關中，我們將要創造一個有兩行的本文內容
layout that functions as a single column layout without media queries.
它的功能和沒有media queries功能的單一行本文內容相同。
Let's first take a look at why we would want to use this approach.
讓我們先來了解為什麼我們會需要用到這種方法。
So far, we've been able to use media queries to create a good experience on small screens.
到目前為止，我們已經能夠應用media queries使之在小螢幕上有好的呈現。
However, without media query support,
然而，如果沒有media query的支援 ，
the small-screen experience varies.
小螢幕的呈現都會不同。
In the Gmail application, we can see
在 Gmail應用程式上，我們可以看到
that our email is zoomed out.
電子郵件被縮小了。
In the small-screen version of outlook.com,
在Outlook.com的小屏幕版本上，
we see that they don't zoom our email,
我們看到電子郵件並沒有被縮小，
but they also don't force our widths at 100%,
但他們也不會強迫將寬度設為100％，
so you would actually have to pan in order to read the email.
所以實際上我們需要滑動來閱讀郵件。
Zoom is the first problem that we want to fix.
縮放成了我們首要解決的問題。
In order to do this, we need to convert our table widths to fluid widths.
為了做到這一點，我們需要轉換表格的寬度為浮動的。
For our header table, we would set the width to 100%
我們的頁首將設置寬度為100％。
and apply a max width of 600 pixels.
並套用其最大寬度為600px。
Looking at that in the Gmail client,
看看在 Gmail的客戶端，
we can now see that there's no more zoom.
現在已經沒有任何的縮放。
One unfortunate thing about lacking media query support
一個關於不支援media query的壞處
is we have no way of conditionally changing our font sizes.
是我們沒有辦法用條件去改變字體大小。
Here, we can see that our title text was set to 74 pixels,
在這裡，我們可以看到我們將標題設定為74px，
and without media queries, it's going to remain that way in every client.
在沒有media queries的情況下，這將在每個裝置上都保持一樣。
This is the first problem that we weren't able to fix.
這是第一個我們無法解決的問題。
However, having the text large makes it more readable than
然而，字體較大也比較容易閱讀
when it's zoomed out and small, and this is a good trade-off.
當其縮小了之後，這是個很好的權衡方式。
Continuing down the content of our email,
繼續往下看郵件的內容，
we would apply those same styles to our table
我們將繼續應用一樣的設定到其他表格上。
that's containing our image.
這一個包含了圖片
So here again, we're applying width of 100%
所以，在此我們將寬度設為100%
and max width of 600 pixels.
和最大寬度為600px。
And this maintains no zoom in Gmail.
一樣在Gmail中沒有縮放。
Without media queries, a table row with two cells will always align horizontally.
在沒有media queries的情況下，表格中的兩列永遠是對齊的。
The content in each of these cells is set to 300 pixels,
文中每一個單元格都設定為300px，
causing a total width of 600 pixels.
這造成總寬度變為600px。
Our available area is only 320 pixels, triggering zoom.
我們可用顯示區域只有320px，這引發了縮小。
We need a way for these two content tables to stack on top of each other without media queries.
我們需要一種方法，在沒有media queries之下使此兩個表格彼此推疊。
Without media queries, table cells won't stack vertically.
沒有media queries，單元表格不會垂直的堆疊在一起。
However, there is a way to make tables stack vertically
然而，有一種方式可以使表格垂直的堆疊。
if there is not enough horizontal space,or stack horizontally if there is.
如果當其沒有足夠的水平空間，或是可以水平的堆疊在可云許的情況下。
The way that we do this is assigning a value of left to the align attribute of a table.
我們的方式是指定表格的屬性為向左對齊。
We have our table of content.
我們有了內容的表格。
We're going to take that table and nest it
我們將使用該表，
and nest it in a table with a width of 300 pixels and set to align left.
將其放入寬度為300px的表中，並設置為向左對齊。
We're then going to take that column
我們將要使用該行列。
and nest it in a container table with a width of 100% and a max width of 600 pixels.
並且放在一個設定寬度為100%，最大寬度為600px的表格。
Next, we're going to repeat the same thing for the second column.
接下來，我們要在第二列重複同樣的事情。
We have our table for content.
我們有內容表格。
We're going to nest that in a column table,
我們要將他放在一個行列表格中，
and then we're going to nest both of those tables in the same container table.
然後我們要這些表格都放入一樣的內容表格中。
Now we have both of our content tables stacked vertically without media queries.
現在我們已經將兩個表格在沒有media queries之下垂直堆疊了。
While we're focused on creating this layout without media queries,
當我們專注在產生一個沒有使用media queries的文本時，
we want to keep in mind how this is going to affect our other clients.
我們要記得這是怎樣的去影響其他的客戶端裝置。
Earlier, we had classes with styles
早些時候，我們在style中加入class
that forced our columns to full width and provided some vertical spacing.
這迫使列要符合寬度且有一些的垂直間距。
To make sure that those are still available for our other clients,
為了確保這些在客戶接收端都還可以適用，
we need to add them back to our tables and cells.
我們需要將他們加到表格和單元格中。
We've fixed our stacking problem,
我們已經解決了堆疊的問題，
but we've created a new problem.
但我們卻創建了一個新的問題。
When the horizontal space isn't enough to hold both columns,
當水平的空間不足以容納兩個列，
but it's bigger than each individual column,
但他又比單一個列還要大，
the two tables are going to align to the left of the client.
這兩個表都會像裝置端的左邊對齊。
If we really want those two columns centered,
如果我們想要這兩列可以置中，
the solution is somewhat hacky.
解決方式是有些的投機。
What we would do is take each table column and wrap it in a div.
我們將每一個表格的列都包進div
We would then apply display: inline-block to those divs.
然後再將 display: inline-block應用到這些div上。
We can then set text-align: center on
這麼一來我們就可以設定 text-align: center 在
the containing cell, which will shift both of those divs to the center.
這些會將divs設定置中的單元格中。
We've now run into another edge case problem.
現在我們進入到另一個邊界問題。
Outlook.com's preprocessor removes margin properties from our inline styles.
outlook.com的預處理器移除了我們在inline style的邊界設定。
However, it won't remove the property if you use a capital "M" for margin.
但是，當我們使用的是"M"argin時，他並不會移除屬性。
To fix the layout for this table,
為了修復本文的格局，
we're going to change the "m" to a capital "M" for Margin: 0 auto.
我們要將小寫的m換成M，Margin:0 auto。
Our multi-column layout is now working as a single column layout without media queries on small screens.
我們原本的多欄佈局本文，現在是以沒有media queries的單行本文的方式顯示在小螢幕上。
Now it's your turn to make that happen in the challenges.
現在是時候輪到你在挑戰中實作了。